dynamsoft.com 2017-10-17

# Privacy Statement

Updated May 12, 2016

Information Collection

Dynamsoft Corporation collects contact information from customers at several different points on our websites: free trial ordering, online support registration and subscription to the news. Dynamsoft respects your privacy and will not give, sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

Information Using and Sharing

The information we collect during your registration process is used to notify users about new products and services or special events. If you do not wish to receive such email messages in the future, you may opt out of these communications by visiting our unsubscribe page.

The information provided is not shared with any third parties for commercial or non-commercial purposes except selected Dynamsoft resellers, distributors and other partners performing services on our behalf.

We may share some of your personal data, such as your email address, with certain selected resellers, distributors and other partners to enable them to contact you on our behalf about products, services or offers we believe are important to you or your business, to fulfill any terms under your licensing and service relationship with Dynamsoft, or to provide you local technical and customer support.

Cookies

Dynamsoft website uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer that identifies your computer to whoever placed the cookie. We use cookies to help monitor the use of our site, so that we can better understand what information is most valuable to users.

Correction/Updating Personal Information

Customers may change their personally identifiable information or draw back their accounts at any time. We will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the information. Change requests should be sent to info@dynamsoft.com.

Policy Updates

We reserve the right to alter or add to this privacy statement at any time, especially as we add new services to our site. Accordingly, please review this part of our site frequently.
